

Dan Nguyen Gia Senior PHP/WordPress Developer

+84 916681139 danhoat@gmail.com 523 Do Xuan Hop, P. Phuoc Long B, Ho Chi Minh City

Skills

WordPress

PHP & MySQL

HTML/CSS

Javascript/jQuery

Git

Languages

English

VietNam

Social

Linkedin linkedin.com/dannguyengia

Github github.com/danngyw

PROFILE

Around 8+ years of extensive experience as a PHP Web Application Developer by developing WordPress themes and plugins. Extensive experience in payment API work and how to implement it. Experience in technical support and can handle almost WordPress,PHP popular issues.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior WordPress Developer at EngineThemes - Ho Chi Minh City

Jun 2013 - Present

EngineThemes is a WordPress application theme creator.

- Develop WordPress themes and plugins and maintain.
- Implement payment gateway for system.
- Using git to deploy and manage source code.
- Technical support work directly with customers via email and help them solve problems. Customize themes or plugins.
- Conduct internal training for developers within the team.

Tools and technologies: WordPress, XML, HTML/CSS, PHP & MYSQL, jQuery, Ajax,Sublime,Photoshop, Bootstraps, Sass.

Key achievement: FreelanceEngine theme, MicrojobEngine theme.

PHP/WordPress Developer at Goscom - Ho Chi Minh City

Jun 2012 - May 2013

Goscom is a software outsourcing company.

- Experience with Xampp (Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP, HTML/CSS).
- Convert PSD file to HTML/CSS template.
- Customize PHP WordPress/Woocommerce and support customers.

EDUCATION

HCMUS - Bachelor's degree - Ho Chi Minh City

Sep 2006 - Jun 2011

Learn programming languages like C/C++/C#/JAVA/ASP.NET and OPP, MVC, algorithms ... Develop simple applications.

PHP SKILLS

- Proficiency in OOP with a good understanding of MVC practices.
- Strong knowledge of RESTful Web Services and JSON.
- Excellent PHP & MySQL, JavaScript, Bootstraps and Sass.
- Good to debug and solve PHP/WordPress problems.
- Experience to implement payment gateway/escrow API(PayPal/Stripe...).